(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) You've got a friend in me You've got
a friend in me When the road looks
rough ahead And you're miles and miles from
your nice home, baby You just remember what
your old pal said, boy You've got a
friend in me No, you've got a friend
in me You've
got a friend in me You've got a
friend in me You've got the troubles, I've
got them too There isn't anything I wouldn't
do for you We stick together and I
see it through Cause you've got a friend
in me You've got a friend in me
Some other folks might be a little bit
smarter than I am, bigger and stronger too,
baby But none of them will ever love
you the way I do, just me and
you, boy And as the years go by
Our friendship will never die You're gonna see
it's our destiny Cause you've got a friend
in me You've got a friend in me
You've got a friend in me